http://cswpc.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This website privacy policy is for www.cswpc.co.uk. The policy details the areas where user privacy is concerned. The policy describes how CSWPC protects and make use of the information you give when you use this website.
If you are asked to provide information when using this website, it will only be used in the ways described in this privacy policy. Users contacting this website and/or its owners do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own risk. Your details are not passed on to any third parties.
This policy is updated from time to time. The latest version is published on this page.
This website privacy policy was updated: March 2018
If you have any questions about this policy, please email us at contactcswpc@gmail.com.
We gather and use certain information about individuals in order to enable certain functions on this website. We also collect information to help us to understand how visitors use this website and to present relevant information to them.
What data we gather
We may collect the following information:
Name, email address, telephone number
Your interest relevant to the club
Website usage data
How we use this data
Collecting this data helps us understand what you are looking from the club, enabling us to deliver improved services and site information.
Specifically, we may use data:
For our own internal records.
To improve the products and services we provide.
To contact you in response to a specific enquiry.
To customise the website for you.
To send you news based emails about information related to the club.
To contact you via email or telephone for reasons associated with the club.
Controlling information about you
When you fill in a form or provide your details on our website, you will see one or more tick boxes allowing you to:
Opt-in to receive marketing communications from us by email or phone
If you have agreed that we can use your information for marketing purposes, you can change your mind easily:
Send an email to contactcswpc@gmail.com
We will never lease, distribute or sell your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or the law requires us to. We will prevent unauthorised disclosure or access to your information.
External links
Our website may contain links to other websites.
The owners of this website cannot guarantee or verify the contents of any external linked websites. Users click on external links at their own risk and CSWPC cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links from this site.
Please note that we have no control of websites outside the CSWPC domain. If you provide information to a website to which we link, we are not responsible for its protection and privacy.
Social media links
CSWPC may also link to social media websites. Please note that the social media platform may track and save your click through to the relevant social media platform account.
CSWPC Swimshop
For club team kit purchases and training equipment, visit our TYR partner,	Allens of Kingsbury >
*** Updated Sportsystems Entry File – July 2019 > ***
Download the meet packs, including entry forms now >
SOCIAL MEDIA COOKIES
PRIVACY POLICY
This site uses cookies:
Find out more.Okay, thanks
